God is still saying something.
On Sunday May 7th 2017, during The SCOAN Live
Sunday Service, Prophet T.B. Joshua gave a
prophecy concerning the outcome of the 2017
French Presidential Election, shortly before
the results were officially announced.
These were his words:
“In Jesus Christ’s name we pray.
Give thanks to God.
There is so much uproar in the French speaking
country.
We look at the two candidates.
For me, immigrants, refugees--- Because my
Father in Heaven was once a refugee too.
So, we pray for any one of them who supports
refugees – like Emmanuel Macron.
We are praying for him and our prayer will
answer!
I will leave it; I will not say more than that.
It is prayer that will put him there, not
anything –
because of his heart for refugees and immigrants.
Half of this world are immigrants and refugees.
Where will they go?
I pray every day for Emmanuel Macron -
I am not a politician - because of what he believes.
What he believes is what my Father in Heaven
believes.
We will see what we can do to protect these
refugees and immigrants.
Many of them – it is not their will to leave
their country; it is war.
When there is war, you run helter-skelter
– anywhere you know you can run to.
We know there are some bad people among the
refugees.
But we cannot say because there are some bad
people that we reject all of them.
I am not saying you should pray for him.
Me – I am praying for him, Emmanuel Macron,
because of what he believes.
I listened to his profile – his belief about
refugees and immigrants.
Today is declaration.
I am praying, not you; I am not saying you because we are not playing politics in the Church.”
That is just what I believe; thank you.